[
  { "question": "Naruto", "answer": "Naruto" },
  { "question": "One Piece", "answer": "Luffy" },
  { "question": "Bleach", "answer": "Ichigo" },
  { "question": "Dragon Ball", "answer": "Goku" },
  { "question": "Hunter x Hunter", "answer": "Gon" },
  { "question": "My Hero Academia", "answer": "Izuku" },
  { "question": "Attack on Titan", "answer": "Eren" },
  { "question": "Death Note", "answer": "Light" },
  { "question": "Fullmetal Alchemist", "answer": "Edward" },
  { "question": "Tokyo Ghoul", "answer": "Ken" },
  { "question": "Demon Slayer", "answer": "Tanjiro" },
  { "question": "Jujutsu Kaisen", "answer": "Yuji" },
  { "question": "Fairy Tail", "answer": "Natsu" },
  { "question": "Black Clover", "answer": "Asta" },
  { "question": "Dr. Stone", "answer": "Senku" },
  { "question": "Blue Lock", "answer": "Isagi" },
  { "question": "Chainsaw Man", "answer": "Denji" },
  { "question": "Mob Psycho 100", "answer": "Shigeo" },
  { "question": "Vinland Saga", "answer": "Thorfinn" },
  { "question": "Fire Force", "answer": "Shinra" },
  { "question": "The Promised Neverland", "answer": "Emma" },
  { "question": "Boruto", "answer": "Boruto" },
  { "question": "Spy x Family", "answer": "Loid" },
  { "question": "Blue Period", "answer": "Yatora" },
  { "question": "Erased", "answer": "Satoru" },
  { "question": "Parasyte", "answer": "Shinichi" },
  { "question": "Noragami", "answer": "Yato" },
  { "question": "Dorohedoro", "answer": "Caiman" },
  { "question": "Pluto", "answer": "Gesicht" },
  { "question": "Monster", "answer": "Tenma" },
  { "question": "Berserk", "answer": "Guts" },
  { "question": "Psycho-Pass", "answer": "Akane" },
  { "question": "Ao Ashi", "answer": "Ashito" },
  { "question": "Kuroko no Basket", "answer": "kuroko" },
  { "question": "Haikyuu!!", "answer": "Shoyo" },
  { "question": "Great Teacher Onizuka", "answer": "Eikichi" },
  { "question": "Gintama", "answer": "Gintoki" },
  { "question": "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure phantom blood", "answer": "Jonathan" },
  { "question": "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure battle tendancy", "answer": "Joseph" },
  { "question": "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure Stardust crusaders", "answer": "Jotaro" },
  { "question": "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure diamond is unbrekable", "answer": "Josuke" },
  { "question": "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure golden wind", "answer": "Giorno" },
  { "question": "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure stone ocean", "answer": "Jolyne" },
  { "question": "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure steel ball run", "answer": "Johnny" },
  { "question": "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure jojolyon", "answer": "Josuke" },
  { "question": "Kill la Kill", "answer": "Ryuko" },
  { "question": "Akame ga Kill!", "answer": "Tatsumi" },
  { "question": "Claymore", "answer": "Clare" },
  { "question": "Gantz", "answer": "Kei" },
  { "question": "Zom 100 bucket list of death", "answer": "Akira" },
  { "question": "Kaiju No. 8", "answer": "Kafka" },
  { "question": "Soul Eater", "answer": "Maka" },
  { "question": "Elfen Lied", "answer": "Lucy" },
  { "question": "Bungou Stray Dogs", "answer": "Atsushi" },
  { "question": "Re:Zero", "answer": "Subaru" },
  { "question": "No Game No Life", "answer": "Sora" },
  { "question": "Future Diary", "answer": "Yukiteru" },
  { "question": "Black Bullet", "answer": "Rentaro" },
  { "question": "Btooom!", "answer": "Ryota" },
  { "question": "91 Days", "answer": "Angelo" },
  { "question": "A Silent Voice", "answer": "Shoya" },
  { "question": "Your Lie in April", "answer": "Kosei" },
  { "question": "Made in Abyss", "answer": "Riko" },
  { "question": "To Your Eternity", "answer": "Fushi" },
  { "question": "March Comes in Like a Lion", "answer": "Rei" },
  { "question": "Ergo Proxy", "answer": "Re-l" },
  { "question": "Durarara!!", "answer": "Mikado" },
  { "question": "Devilman Crybaby", "answer": "Akira" },
  { "question": "Baki", "answer": "Baki" },
  { "question": "Hellsing", "answer": "Alucard" },
  { "question": "Trigun", "answer": "Vash" },
  { "question": "Samurai Champloo", "answer": "Mugen" },
  { "question": "Basilisk", "answer": "Gennosuke" },
  { "question": "Rurouni Kenshin", "answer": "Kenshin" },
  { "question": "Inuyasha", "answer": "Inuyasha" },
  { "question": "Yu Yu Hakusho", "answer": "Yusuke" },
  { "question": "Beelzebub", "answer": "Oga" },
  { "question": "Katekyo Hitman Reborn!", "answer": "Tsuna" },
  { "question": "Nana", "answer": "Nana" },
  { "question": "Clannad", "answer": "Tomoya" },
  { "question": "Angel Beats!", "answer": "Otonashi" },
  { "question": "The Rising of the Shield Hero", "answer": "Naofumi" },
  { "question": "Overlord", "answer": "Ainz" },
  { "question": "Konosuba", "answer": "Kazuma" },
  { "question": "That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime", "answer": "Rimuru" },
  { "question": "The Seven Deadly Sins", "answer": "Meliodas" },
  { "question": "Hajime no Ippo", "answer": "Ippo" },
  { "question": "Eyeshield 21", "answer": "Sena" },
  { "question": "Shaman King", "answer": "Yoh" },
  { "question": "Yakusoku no Neverland", "answer": "Emma" },
  { "question": "Sakamoto days", "answer": "Taro" },
  { "question": "Maou Gakuin", "answer": "Anos" },
  { "question": "Rainbow: Nisha Rokubou no Shichinin", "answer": "Mario" },
  { "question": "Shinsekai Yori", "answer": "Saki" },
  { "question": "Kaiji", "answer": "Kaiji" },
  { "question": "Akagi", "answer": "Shigeru" },
  { "question": "Kino no Tabi", "answer": "Kino" },
  { "question": "Casshern Sins", "answer": "Casshern" },
  { "question": "Ergo Proxy", "answer": "Re-l" },
  { "question": "Moi quand je me r√©incarne en slime", "answer": "Limule" },
  { "question": "Now and Then, Here and There", "answer": "Shu" },
  { "question": "Houseki no Kuni", "answer": "Phos" },
  { "question": "Mushishi", "answer": "Ginko" },
  { "question": "The Tatami Galaxy", "answer": "Watashi" },
  { "question": "Kaiba", "answer": "Kaiba" },
  { "question": "Serial Experiments Lain", "answer": "Lain" },
  { "question": "Zankyou no Terror", "answer": "Nine" },
  { "question": "Welcome to the NHK", "answer": "Tatsuhiro" },
  { "question": "Aoi Bungaku Series", "answer": "Yozo" },
  { "question": "Boogiepop Phantom", "answer": "Boogiepop" },
  { "question": "Shigurui", "answer": "Fujiki" },
  { "question": "Texhnolyze", "answer": "Ichise" },
  { "question": "Haibane Renmei", "answer": "Rakka" },
  { "question": "Blame!", "answer": "Killy" },
  { "question": "Dorohedoro", "answer": "Caiman" },
  { "question": "Ajin", "answer": "Kei" },
  { "question": "Gleipnir", "answer": "Shuichi" },
  { "question": "Devils' Line", "answer": "Yuki" },
  { "question": "Inuyashiki", "answer": "Ichiro" },
  { "question": "Kokkoku", "answer": "Juri" },
  { "question": "Bokurano", "answer": "Jun" },
  { "question": "Ousama Ranking", "answer": "Bojji" },
  { "question": "ID: Invaded", "answer": "Sakaido" },
  { "question": "Sonny Boy", "answer": "Nagara" },
  { "question": "No.6", "answer": "Shion" },
  { "question": "Gankutsuou", "answer": "Albert" },
  { "question": "Shiki", "answer": "Natsuno" },
  { "question": "Vivy: Fluorite Eye's Song", "answer": "Vivy" },
  { "question": "Karakuri Circus", "answer": "Masaru" },
  { "question": "Hell Girl", "answer": "Ai" },
  { "question": "Texhnolyze", "answer": "Ichise" },
  { "question": "Danganronpa", "answer": "Makoto" },
  { "question": "God Eater", "answer": "Lenka" },
  { "question": "Tokyo Magnitude 8.0", "answer": "Mirai" },
  { "question": "Shinreigari", "answer": "Tarou" },
  { "question": "Yokohama Kaidashi Kikou", "answer": "Alpha" },
  { "question": "Mahou Shoujo Tokushusen Asuka", "answer": "Asuka" },
  { "question": "Kujira no Kora wa Sajou ni Utau", "answer": "Chakuro" },
  { "question": "Gasaraki", "answer": "Yushiro" },
  { "question": "Bounen no Xamdou", "answer": "Akiyuki" },
  { "question": "C: The Money of Soul and Possibility Control", "answer": "Kimimaro" }
]
